Hello? (Subtitle Revised by HchC)
喂?
What do you look like?
你長什麼樣?
Talk louder!
大聲點
I can't hear you!
我聽不到
Hey, hello!
嘿,喂!
Hello! I can't hear you!
喂!我聽不到你說話
Five.
5個
I don't know.
不知道
Get her in focus! Here I come!
讓她精神集中點! 我來了
Open up! Shit!
開門,糟了
Jesus H. Christ! What are you--?
上帝啊,你怎麼--?
What happened?
怎麼了?
Now he's got pressure. He has a receiver!
現在他有壓力了,他拿到了球
When it's time to relax
當需要放鬆時
One beer stands clear
一罐啤酒足矣
Oh, damn it!
哦,該死的
Tweety?
特悌?
Oh, shit, Tweety! Couldn't you have waited for a school day?
哦,該死,特悌,你就不能再等一個教學日嗎?
Won't you please
請不要
Who the hell is this guy?
這傢伙是誰?
What the hell's going on?
發生什麼了?
Freeling, what's goin' on here?
富勒裡, 怎麼回事?
I apologize! My neighbor's on the same remote!
我道歉 我鄰居也是同一個頻段
I bet my life on this game! Are you kiddin' me?
我為這場比賽連命都賭上了,你開玩笑吧
Hi, Ben. We got a good football game goin' on here.
本,我們那正在放一場精彩的球賽
My kids wanna watch "Mr. Rogers."
我的孩子要看"羅傑先生"
I don't care what you're watchin'! Just show some mercy with that thing!
我不在乎你要看什麼,你就算是可憐可憐我們
Come on, Steve!
別啊,史迪夫
Move your set.
把你的遙控器拿開
- Move yours, Ben. - There it is. Don't move.
- 拿開,本 - 就這樣,別換了
Tweety doesn't like that smell.
特悌不喜歡這個味道
Sweetheart, Tweety can't smell a thing.
甜心,特悌聞不到什麼味道
Put a flower with him.
給他獻朵花吧
A flower?
一朵花?
For when he's hungry.
為了他生氣的時候
For when he's lonely.
為了他不再孤單
For when it's nighttime.
為了他將度過的長夜.
Oh, it's okay.
沒事了
Now I lay me down to sleep...
現在我躺下長眠...
I pray the Lord my soul to keep.
我祈禱主寬恕我的靈魂
- Oh, brother. - Stifle it.
- 哦,天哪 - 忍著點
If I should die before I wake...
如果我在醒來之際死去...
It did.
會的
I pray the Lord my soul to take.
我請求主帶走我的靈魂
That was lovely. Lovely, honey.
你這樣很可愛,很可愛
Mom, when it rots, can we dig up the bones?
媽,等屍體腐爛之後能把骨頭挖出來嗎?
Robbie! Will you come on down out of the tree?
羅比,你就不能從樹上下來?
E. Buzz!
E. Buzz!
Can I have a goldfish now?
我們現在能養條金魚了嗎
Come and get it.
來吃啊
You're overfeeding them.
你把他們喂的太飽了
Tweety Two and Tweety Three want seconds.
二十二和二十三還想要
You know what happens when you overfeed goldfish?
你知道怎麼回事嗎,你喂的太多了?
They grow up to be... sharks!
他們要長成...鯊魚
Good night.
晚安
Mom, there's a big storm headed this way.
媽媽.有大風暴要來了
You'll be asleep by the time it gets here if you hurry.
如果你們快點 風暴在你們入睡之後才會來
Come on. In you go.
來,到被子裡去
Good night, sweetie.
晚安,寶貝
Okay, lights out.
好,關燈了
Closet light!
燈滅了!
My fault.
我的錯
Turn it on, Mommy!
開燈,媽媽
That enough?
夠了吧?
- Okay? - Good night, Mom.
- 行吧? - 晚安,媽
Night, Mommy.
晚安.媽媽
Good night.
晚安
Either I'm dead or I'm crazy.
我死了或是瘋了
You're not crazy, Pete.
皮特,你沒有瘋
You mean I'm dead?
那你是說我死了?
I'm--
我--
You mean-- You mean this is for good?
你是說-- 你是說這是好事?
Sleepwalking.
夢遊啊
Nocturnal somnambulism. You know what?
晚上的夢遊症,你不知道嗎?
I will bet you anything it's genetic.
我跟你打賭,這是遺傳的
I mean, Carol Anne last night and all last week.
卡羅爾昨晚就是,整個星期的晚上都在夢遊
And me when I was ten.
我十歲的時候也是
- Would you deal with this? - Sure.
- 你能搞定這個嗎? - 好
You know...
你知道..
once I slept-walked four blocks...
一次我夢遊外出...
and I fell asleep in the back of this guy's car.
在一個夥計的車的後座上睡著了
He drove all the way to work before discovering me.
你一直開著車,去工作也沒發現我
God, I woke up, I started screaming.
天,然後我醒來了,開始狂叫
People came running, called the cops.
人們跑過來,叫了警察
The cops took this poor dude downtown.
警察把這個可憐的花花公子帶到市區
- My father, Ed-- - Big.
- 我父親, Ed-- -Big.
Big Ed has me examined for bruises and hickeys.
Big Ed 還檢查了我有沒有受傷, 有沒有被侮辱
God, I was so embarrassed!
天啊,真是太尷尬了
Oh, shit, Steve.
哦,天,史迪夫
What if we dig the pool, you know...
如果我們挖個水池.你知道...
and Carol Anne sleepwalks and falls into it before there's any water?
在沒有水之前,卡羅爾夢遊時掉進去了會怎麼樣?
Oh, honey, no.
哦,親愛的,別這樣
Have you ever dove off a three-meter board, sweetheart?
甜心,你滑過3米長的滑板嗎?
- What's three meters? - It's about ten feet.
- 三米是多少? - 十英尺
Let's dig the pool closer to the house and let the kids jump off the roof.
我們把水池挖的離屋子近點 這樣孩子們就可以從屋頂上跳下去了
No, honey, honey, honey.
別,親愛的
A three-meter board is like an air pocket, sweetheart.
甜心,3米長的滑板就像個空氣袋
When you dive off, it's like free-falling, okay?
當你跳水時就像自由落體一樣?
You gotta get your feet in position. Three meters.
你要站好位置,3米遠
Honey, your diving days are over.
親愛的,你的跳水生涯已經結束了
We're talkin' Olympics, Diane, okay?
我們在談論奧林匹克,達尼,知道吧
Let me see your tuck position.
讓我看看你的起跳位置
We can jackknife into the swan.
我們像天鵝一樣展開
Twist, turn...
收縮,轉身...
and splash!
然後跳出去
Honey, it's right to the Nautilus machine.
親愛的,去鸚鵡螺號是對的
Look at this, honey. Before, after.
看這個,收縮,伸展
- Don't. - I love you.
- 別了 - 我愛你
Oh, God, I love it when you talk dirty!
天,我喜歡你說髒話的樣子
Storm is coming closer.
風暴越來越近了
Hey, partner.
嘿, 搭檔.
Hi, honey.
嘿,親愛的
Is everything okay?
一切還好吧?
It's thundering.
在打雷
Come on. Hop up.
來,起來
I'm the wind and you're the feather. Say good night to Mom.
你是風,我是風中的羽毛 跟媽媽說晚安
- Good night, Mom. - Good night, sweetheart.
- 晚安.媽媽 - 晚安,寶貝
Here we go.
走咯
I don't like the tree, Dad.
我不喜歡那根樹
That's an old tree. It's been around here a long time.
那是根老樹了,在這很久了
It was here before my company built the neighborhood.
在我的朋友成為鄰居前就在這
I don't like its arms.
我不喜歡它的手臂
- It knows I live here, doesn't it? - It knows everything about us.
- 它知道我住在這裡,是吧? - 它知道我們的一切
That's why I built the house next to it, so it could protect us.
那就是我在它旁邊建房子的緣故, 它能保護我們
You and Carol Anne and Dana and your mom and me.
你,卡羅爾,達納,你媽媽和我
It's a very wise old tree.
這是根老而智慧的樹
It looks at me. It knows I live here.
它看著我,它知道我在這
I think the storm's gonna pass us.
我想,風暴會掠過我們而去
How do you know?
你怎麼知道的?
'Cause I can count.
我能算出
You know what you do?
你知道怎麼做?
When you see the lightning...
看到閃電時...
you count 'til you hear the thunder.
就開始數,知道聽到雷聲
If you can count higher each time, that means the storm's movin' away.
如果數的多說明風暴遠了
Wanna try it?
想試試嗎?
We need some lightning.
需要一些閃電啊
Wait. It's comin'.
等等,來了
Okay, count. One, two, three.
好,開始數,1,2,3
Next time, you'll be able to count to at least four or five. Bet you.
跟你打賭,下次肯定可以數到4或者5
Daddy, it's for you.
爸,找你的
Tell them to take a message, sweet pea.
讓他們留個信,親愛的
My dad wants to take a message.
我爸讓你們留話
Night.
晚安
It's too hot.
太熱了
Okay. Night, angel.
好,晚安,小天使
- Happy dreams, okay? - Night, Daddy.
- 做個好夢,好嗎? - 晚安,爸
One...
1...
two...
2...
three--
3--
I did not. Come on!
我沒有.少來了
- Good night, Dana. - Good night, Dad.
- 晚安,達尼 - 晚安.爸
- Get off the phone, Dana. - Okay, Dad.
- 別打電話了,達尼 - 好的,爸
One...
1...
two--
2--
Three...
3...
four--
4--
Five--
5--
They're here.
他們來了
Listen to me, Jeff. No, I'm not kidding.
聽我說,傑夫 不,我不開玩笑
I know. How could anybody sleep through a 6.5?
我知道,但誰在6.5級的風暴中還睡的著呢?
There was damage. Yeah, the bedroom. There's stuff in pieces all over.
臥室受到損害,碎片到處都是
We're listening to the radio. There's nothing on the radio at all.
我們在聽收音機,但是什麼都沒有
You are so obnoxious! You drive me nuts!
你真討厭,讓我瘋了
Force field.
力場
- You are so obnoxious. - Got my nose.
- 你真討厭 - 擊中我的鼻子了
This means war, and I mean it!
這意味著戰爭,我也這麼認為
- Hey, watch out. - Honey, chew your food ten times.
- 嘿,看著點 - 寶貝,你應該把食物咀嚼10次
You're a big barf bag.
你像個嘔吐袋
You're a doggie bag.
你才像
- I won't eat it. - There you go.
- 我不吃了 - 你要吃的
Sweetheart, last night when you said, "They're here"--
甜心,昨晚你說 ''他們來了''之時--
Can I take my goldfish to school?
我能把金魚帶到學校去嗎?
Maybe the fault line runs directly under our house. Wouldn't that be a scream?
也許出問題的地方正好在房子下 但那些不用發出尖叫聲吧?
The ceiling got crumbs all over my bed.
天花板一直在我床頭響
Remember last night when you woke up and said, "They're here"?
記得你昨晚醒來說"他們來了"嗎?
Who did you mean? Who's here?
你說誰呢,誰來了?
The TV people.
電視裡的人
- She's stoned. - What do you know?
- 她醉了 - 你怎麼知道?
More than you! Ask Dad!
比你強! 問爸爸吧!
- "Ask Dad!"
- ''問爸爸吧'' - ''問爸爸吧!''
"Ask Dad!"
''問爸爸吧!''
It's not my mess!
不是我的錯
Thanks a lot, jerko. I've got class in 20 minutes.
真是太感謝你,笨蛋,20分鐘後我要去上學
Give me this before you cut yourself.
自責之前把這交給我處理吧
Did the earth move for you?
地球是為你而運轉的嗎?
It wasn't quite the same thing for us, Jeff. Huh?
傑夫,這對我們來說不是同樣的事情?
Okay. Yeah, right. Okay.
好,對,就是的
- Give me that before you cut yourself. - It's not my fault.
- 我來處理這些 - 不是我的錯
Bye, sweet pea. I'm outta here.
再見,我走了
- Bye, honey. - I'm outta here.
- 再見,甜心 - 我也走了.
- You I can handle. - I got school.
- 我可以送你 - 我去學校了
- Well, breakfast first. - All right. I'll just flunk.
- 好,先吃早餐 - 好,那我就不及格了
It happens on every job.
每種工作都會有意外發生
Look at this!
看這個
I love that swing.
我喜歡那小妞
I love you. I love you.
我愛你,我愛你
I love it.
我喜歡
E. Buzz, no, no! Get down.
E. Buzz, 不不, 下來
Carol Anne, I've told you guys to push your chairs in when you're done.
卡羅爾,我叫你們吃完後把椅子放進去的
Honey, you're gonna ruin your eyes. This is not good for you.
你會毀了你的眼睛的,這樣不好
What's the matter?
怎麼了啊?
What are you doing?
你幹什麼?
- How is it? - Great, Mrs. Freeling.
- 如何? - 很棒, 富勒裡女士.
- Okay, Bluto, give me my cup. - You sure make good coffee.
- 好,布努托,把杯子給我 - 你的咖啡不錯
Oh, Jesus! Don't do that, honey.
天,別那樣
You wanna see Mommy lying in a cigar box covered with licorice?
你想把媽媽嚇死嗎?
Did you do this?
是你做的?
You guys.
你們啊
I asked you not to pull the chairs out.
我叫你們別把椅子拉出來
The TV people?
電視人?
Do you see them?
你看見他們了?
Do you?
有嗎?
I think you're really gonna enjoy this kitchen.
我想你們肯定會很喜歡這個廚房的
This is our latest development. We call this phase four.
最新裝修過,我們管這叫第四代
Where do you live, Mr. Freeling?
你住哪?, 富勒裡先生?
We were the first family to set up house in the Cuesta Verde Estates.
我們是第一批住到佛得角山脈的人
Oh, phase one.
第一代
We had to pass through my neighborhood to get here.
我要穿過鄰居的房子才能到這
Oh, that area with the lived-in look.
那塊有聖靈的地方
It has that, but in a couple of months you won't be able to distinguish...
是有那麼個說法,但是很快就不能分辨...
phase one from phase three to phase--
第一代,第二代和第三代了--
We have a saying around here.
我們這有句諺語
"The grass grows greener on every side."
''草在每邊都長的更綠.''
- That's the way I feel about it. - I can't tell one house from the other.
- 那就是我摸索出來的 - 我分不清這些房子
I think you're right.
我想你是對的
But I think our construction standards are really very liberal.
但是我覺得我們的建築標準還是很寬大的
I have this neighbor, and he built his Jacuzzi in his bedroom...
我有個鄰居,他在自家的浴室裡按了個 極可意牌浴缸...
and it has a running aqueduct connected to a wading pool outside.
它的出水管連在外面的淺水池
It's built half in and half out of his living room.
一半在屋子裡,一半在外面
It was featured in last month's issue of "Town and Country."
還上了昨日"城市與鄉村"的封頁
I'll show you the den.
我帶你去看看
Honey, come here, quick!
甜心,過來,快
- Hurry, before it stops again! - But the cans--
-快帶你,在停止之前 - 但是這些罐子--
- Easy. - All right.
- 放鬆 - 好
Just stand right here, okay?
站這吧?
I've kept Dana and Robbie out of this, but Carol Anne was here so she knows.
我沒讓達納和羅比知道,但是卡羅爾在這 所以她看見了
Dana would blab, and Robbie would be up for three weeks.
達納不會保密,而羅比肯定要嚇死
I think you should sit down.
我想你應該坐下
Now just stand, okay?
就站著,行嗎?
Now just be calm.
現在冷靜下來
Now reach back into our past when you used to have an open mind.
當你放開思維時想想我們的過去
Remember that?
記得吧?
Just try to use that for the next couple of minutes.
下幾分鐘都要那麼想
- Okay? - Okay.
- 好嗎? - 好
Mother didn't cook any dinner.
媽媽沒給做晚餐
We'll go to Pizza Hut, okay?
我們去吃比薩吧?
Now just look.
看著
Just look. Just watch.
只要看著
Come here, sweetheart.
過來,寶貝
Honey, could you move the chair out of the way...
你能把椅子移開...
and just stay down there?
然後坐在那行嗎?
- Let's show Daddy. - I'm hungry.
- 讓爸爸看看 - 我餓了
Now don't argue with Mommy.
別跟媽媽爭了
Let's just do this once.
我們再做一遍
Okay, here we go.
好,開始了
I want pepperoni pizza.
我想要意大利香腸比薩
Mommy, that burns.
媽媽,熱
The floor needs more wax. Steven, you do it.
地板還要打點臘,史迪夫,你來
Honey, try.
寶貝,試試
It's like there's this tickling...
好像有種迴旋力...
right in here, and it starts to pull you.
就在這,開始拉你
It pulls you, and suddenly it's like there's no air...
然後就好像突然沒有了空氣...
except that you can breathe, and you're getting pulled along--
除非你能呼吸, 然後你開始感覺被拉下來--
- Hi, Ben. - Mr. Tuthill, hi.
- 嘿 本. - 杜希爾先生, 嘿
My TV's not on, so if you're havin' problems with your set--
我的電視沒開,所以如果你的遙控器有什麼問題--
It's nothing like that. Diane and I were just wondering--
不是這個 戴安和我想知道--
-This will sound strange coming from me. -I doubt that.
-這聽起來比較荒唐 -我也不相信
The mosquitoes are awful.
蚊子太恐怖了
They're chowin' down.
它們真該死
I've never been bothered by 'em.
它們從不來煩我
I don't think I've ever been bitten by one of 'em.
我覺得自己沒被咬過
As far as I know, nobody in my family's ever been affected by 'em.
據我所知,我們家還沒被咬過
Mosquito ever suck on you, son?
蚊子從沒咬過你,是吧兒子?
- I don't know, Dad. - He don't know.
- 我不知道,爸爸 - 他不知道
Look.
看
I'm sorry.
抱歉
Uh, Mr. Tuthill, look.
嗯, 杜希爾先生,看
We were just-- What we were wondering--
我們只是-- 我們想知道的是--
Diane, my wife, and I were wondering, Ben...
戴安,我的妻子, 和我想知道,本...
somethin' funny's goin' on here next door.
隔壁有些有趣的事情發生
Somethin', uh--
有些--
We were wondering if maybe you had experienced any disturbances lately.
我們想知道你們最近有沒有被什麼東西騷擾
What kind of disturbances?
什麼騷擾?
Um, oh, you know, like...
你知道...
dishes or furniture moving around by themselves.
像盤子啊傢具啊自己移動
Don't scratch. You're gonna infect 'em.
別抓,會影響痊癒的
Just let me put this on.
讓我給你塗上
- Don't. - Boy, did I feel like a fool.
- 別 - 我像個傻瓜
I'm sorry, but I had to say something. We were losing blood.
抱歉,但是得塗上,我想有點失血
- We'll keep this thing in the family. - Don't scratch.
- 這事兒還得出現在我們家 - 別抓
Tomorrow I'll call somebody.
明天我去叫幾個人
Who, for instance? I already looked in the Yellow Pages.
比如,誰呢? 我已經看過黃頁了
Furniture movers we got. Strange phenomena, there's no listing.
給我們搬傢具得人 真奇怪,也沒有清單
One, one thousand, two, one thousand...
1,1千,2,2千...
three, one thousand, four, one thousand...
3,3千,4,4千...
five, one thousand--
5,5千--
Honey, look.
看
I lived with this freaky thing all day and nothing bad happened.
我天天遇到這種變態的事情但是也沒什麼壞處
It's like another side of nature, a side that we're not qualified to understand.
這好像就是大自然的另一方面, 一個我們沒資格瞭解的方面
When you overreact, it makes what happened much too important.
當你過度反映,那麼發生的就很重要
No one's goin' in the kitchen 'til I know what's happening.
我知道發生了什麼之前不准進廚房
One, one thousand, two, one thousand...
1,1千,2,2千...
three, one thousand, four, one thousand--
3,3千,--
One, one thousand, two, one thousand, three--
1,1千,2,1千,3---
two, one thousand--
1,1千,2,2千.--
Help me!
救命
- Help me, Dad! - Be careful!
- 救我,爸爸 - 小心
Dad, come on!
爸,快點
Help me!
救命
He's coming!
他來了
It's taking me in!
它要吃下我了
- He's coming! - It's hurting me!
- 他來了 - 它弄傷我了
- Steven, hurry! - Dad, help me!
- 史迪夫,快點 - 爸爸,快救我
- Hold on! - Hold on to him!
- 堅持住 - 抓住他
Hold me, Dad!
抓住我,爸爸!
- I got him! - My leg!
- 抓住了 - 我的腿
Dad, my leg!
爸爸,我的腿
Help me, Dad!
救命啊,爸爸
Look, Mom, Dad! It's a tornado!
看,爸媽,是龍捲風
It must've just skimmed us. There wouldn't be a house left if--
它剛才肯定是忽略了我們 不會有一幢房子倖免的--
I left her upstairs!
我把她留在了樓上
Baby, we're coming!
寶貝,我們來了
- I'll go check the kitchen. - No! I'll do it!
- 我去查廚房 - 不,我去
You check your room.
你檢查自己的臥室
Baby?
寶貝?
Sweetheart?
甜心?
Did you find her?
找到她了?
I've looked everywhere. This is crazy.
我哪都找了,真是瘋了
Oh, my-- My God.
噢,我的天
The swimming pool.
泳池
Be careful, honey!
小心,親愛的
Mommy!
媽咪
Nothing!
沒事
Thank God.
謝天謝地
What?
什麼?
Oh, Carol Anne, thank God! Baby!
噢,卡羅爾,謝天謝地
Baby, where are you?
寶貝,你在哪?
- Mommy, come over here! - What is it?
- 媽咪.過來 - 什麼?
What, baby?
什麼,寶貝?
I can't hear you, Mommy.
媽媽,我聽不到
Where are you?
你在哪?
I can't hear you, Mommy!
我聽不到你,媽媽
What members of the household are involved...
有哪些家庭成員被牽扯進去...
and what are their ages?
他們都多大了?
There's Diane, my wife. She's 31.
有達尼,我的妻子,31歲
Uh, 32. I'm sorry.
啊,是32,對不起
My oldest daughter, Dana. She's 16.
我最大的女兒,16歲
My son, Robert, is eight.
我的兒子,羅伯特,8歲
Five.
5個
Has there been any publicity about these events?
這件事公開過嗎?
Absolutely nothing.
絕對沒有
Can you be reasonably sure...
你敢確定...
of not letting any get started?
沒有理由讓這些發生?
That's the last thing we want.
這就是我們最後希望的
We haven't even gone to the police.
我們還沒去過警察局呢
Would your family welcome...
你的家庭會歡迎...
a serious investigation of these disturbances...
一個對此事的嚴密調查嗎...
by someone who can make firsthand observations?
這項調查可以讓他們掌握第一手資料?
Look, Dr. Lesh, we don't care about the disturbances--
聽著, 萊斯博士, 我們不在乎那些--
the pounding and the flashing...
打擾你們的的重擊,...
the screaming, the music.
尖叫,音樂
We just want you to find our little girl.
我們只要你們找到我的小女兒
I guess I should warn you that...
我想應該警告你們...
we keep the room locked off from the rest of the house.
我們把這間屋子鎖起來跟其他房間隔開
Robbie's sleeping with us now, and Dana spends a lot of time with friends.
羅比跟我們睡, 達納多跟朋友呆著一起
How many disturbances have you recorded in the room?
這種事情一共發生過多少回?
We don't go in the room anymore.
我們不進那個屋子了
Mr. Freeling, we'll record any psychotropic energy or event.
富勒裡先生,我們會記錄下任何物理的能量 變化和力場波動
Yes, Ryan photographed an extraordinary episode on a case in Redlands.
是, 賴安曾在紅土地上拍下了 一起事件十分有趣的環節
That's right. It was a child's toy, a very small Matchbox vehicle.
是的,是一個小孩子的玩具, 一個火柴盒大小的交通工具
It rolled seven feet across a linoleum surface.
它滾了7英尺,穿過了一張油布毯
The duration of the event was seven hours.
這持續了7個小時
Seven hours for what?
怎麼會7個小時?
For the vehicle to complete the distance.
讓它花時間完成這段距離
Of course, this would never register on the naked eye...
當然,一般的肉眼難以相信...
but I have it recorded on time-lapse camera.
但是我用高速照相機拍下了
It's fantastic.
太奇妙了
We've been trying to hold ourselves together as a family.
我們一直努力維護這個家庭
Of course, no one's been sleeping much.
當然,大家現在睡的都很少
Steven has missed so much work.
史迪夫也錯過了那麼多工作
But he's been wonderful. Really wonderful.
但是他確實很想知道這是什麼原因
How long have you been investigating haunted houses?
你調查鬧鬼的房子有多久了?
- Mrs. Freeling-- - Diane.
- 富勒裡女士-- - 戴安
The determination as to whether your home is haunted is not very easy.
下決定說你的屋子鬧鬼還不是件很容易的事情
What I meant to say was...
我的意思是...
it might very well be a poltergeist intrusion...
可能是個惡作劇...
instead of a classic haunting.
而不是所謂的鬧鬼
There's a difference?
有區別嗎?
Did you see that?
看見了嗎?
There'll be two more. They travel in pairs.
會有兩次的,總是這樣
Dr. Casey.
凱西博士.
Gotta be quicker than that.
應該行動快點.
It's electrical. You can smell the charge.
是電路原因,你可以聞到
What about poltergeists?
是不是會鬧惡作劇的鬼?
Poltergeists are usually associated with an individual.
鬧惡作劇的鬼通常跟個人聯繫在一起的
Haunting seem to be connected...
鬧鬼通常跟...
with an area, a house, usually.
屋裡一塊區域有關
Poltergeist disturbances have a fairly short duration.
這種騷亂一般時間很短
Perhaps a couple of months.
大概2個月
Haunting can go on for years.
而鬧鬼則可能持續幾年
Are you telling me that all of this could just suddenly end at any time?
你是說這些事情可以很快就結束?
Yes, it could.
是的
Unless it's a haunting.
除非這不是一般的鬧鬼
But haunting don't usually revolve around living people.
但是鬧鬼一般不會跟活人扯上關係啊
Then we don't have much time, because my daughter is alive in this house.
我們時間不多了,我女兒還活在這房子裡
While trying to escape from an unknown assailant.
她正在躲避莫名其妙的攻擊
Marshall is listed as critical and under intensive care.
馬歇爾別確定病危得到嚴密的照顧
This is probably gonna seem a little strange.
這有點奇怪
We hear better on this channel.
這個頻道聽起來好些
Don't ask me why.
別問我原因
Well...
嗯...
I guess I'll call her.
我想我對她說幾句話
It's Mommy, sweetheart.
是媽媽,甜心
We wanna talk to you.
我們想和你談話
Please answer me, baby.
請回答我,寶貝
Please answer me.
請回答我
Please talk to me, bunny.
小乖乖,跟我說話啊
Look at the dog.
看看這狗
Are you with us now?
你和我們在一起嗎?
Can you say hello to Daddy?
你能跟爸爸打聲招呼嗎?
Hello, Daddy.
嘿,爸爸
Hello, sweet pea.
嘿,小寶貝
It's Mommy, sweetheart.
是媽媽,甜心
Hello, Mommy.
喂,媽媽
Hello, baby.
喂,寶貝
Can you see me?
你能看見我嗎?
Can you see Mommy?
你能看見媽媽嗎?
Mommy, where are you? Where are you?
媽媽,你在哪?
We're home, baby. We're home.
我們在家,寶貝
- Can you find a way home to us, baby? - Mommy, where are you?
- 你能找到回家的路,回到我們身邊嗎? - 媽媽,你在哪?
I can't find you! I can't!
我找不到你
I'm afraid of the light, Mommy!
我害怕燈光,媽媽
I'm afraid of the light!
我怕光
Tell her to stay away from the light!
叫她離光遠點
- Maybe it's a way out. - It is, but not for her.
- 也許這是出來的路 - 也許是,但不是給她的
Tell her quickly.
快告訴她
- Stay away from the light! - Tell her, Diane.
- 離光遠點 - 告訴她,戴安
Stay away from the light!
離光遠點
The light is dangerous! Don't go near it!
光很危險,別靠近
- Don't even look at the light! - I don't believe it.
- 甚至別看一眼 - 我不信
The voice could be coming from a CB transmitter.
聲音有可能是通過民用波段傳過來的
This isn't a hoax!
這不是什麼愚弄
What the hell is this?
那是什麼?
Anything?
是什麼?
- Nothing's registered. - Mommy, there's somebody here.
- 什麼都不敢確定 - 媽媽,這有人
Mommy, is that you?
是你嗎?
No, it's not Mommy. Who is it, Dr. Lesh?
不是媽媽 這是誰, 萊斯博士?
- Who's with you, baby? - Who's with you?
- 誰跟你在一起?
Somebody's coming! Help me, please!
有人來了,救我啊
My God! My baby!
我的天,我的孩子
You bastards! She's just a baby!
你個混蛋,她只是孩子啊
Help her! Can't you hear what's happening?
救她,難道你沒聽出發生了什麼?
Listen!
聽
Get away from me! Leave me alone!
別碰我,離我遠點
Mommy, help me!
媽媽,救我啊
She just moved through me.
她剛才穿過我了
My God!
天
I felt her.
我感覺到她了
I can smell her!
我可以嗅到她
It's her!
是她
Smell my clothes. She's all over me.
聞我的衣服 她跟我同在
- It's her. - My God.
- 是她 - 我的天
It's her. I felt her.
是她,我感覺到了
It is. It's her.
就是
It's my baby.
是我的孩子
She went through my soul.
她穿過了我的靈魂
I can't hear her anymore. Honey?
我再也聽不到她了?
Where exactly do you suppose Carol Anne was playing...
當她從視線中消失的時候...
when she vanished from sight?
她是在哪玩的?
Where was Carol Anne playing when she disappeared?
卡羅爾消失的時候在哪玩?
Her bedroom closet.
最靠近她的臥室
Let's go up there.
我們去哪
They won't let you in.
他們不讓你進
We'll just see about that.
我們要去看看
Whatever happened to you?
你怎麼啦?
I was just about to check out the kid's bedroom when-- I don't know.
我不知道-我只是去檢查孩子的房間
Something took a bite outta me.
有東西咬了我一口
You got bit?
你被咬了?
-That or the world's worst muscle spasm. -Let's have a look.
-世界上最恐怖的肌肉痙攣 -我看看
-Think we'll spend the night downstairs. -No. Wrong.
-想想我們還是在樓下睡覺 -不,錯了
Honey, you take Dana and Robbie and go and spend tonight in town.
甜心,你帶著孩子倆去鎮裡過夜
I am not leaving here without Carol Anne.
我不離開卡羅爾
Mom, Dad, I can't stay here anymore.
爸媽,這我再也呆不下了
You go, baby, go.
好,寶貝,你們去
I'm not gonna leave anybody in this house alone.
我不會丟下這房子裡的任何人的
Can we talk to you?
能和你談談嗎?
Let's go.
走
- Any movement from those things? - There's been some ionization flux.
- 這些東西動了嗎? - 能測到一些點離子
I'd like to make sure they're not caused by humidity from structure leakage...
我想確定是不是因為潮濕導致結構的變化...
but I'm not goin' up there to find out.
但我不去那查什麼原因
We have got much more than the paranormal episode taking place here.
這兒發生的事情已經超過正常範圍了
There is a measurable physical science in this house...
這房子裡的科學力量...
that goes far beyond the creaking doors or cold spots I've experienced.
已經遠遠超過我遇到過的那些奇怪現象
The voice on television. Where is it coming from?
電視上的聲音 它是從哪來的?
The absence of a signal on a channel that is not receiving a broadcast...
沒有接受任何電視信號...
means that it can receive a lot of noise from many things, like short waves.
意味著它可以從很多東西那接受到聲音.比如短波
Solar disturbances, car ignition sparkings.
太陽黑子波動 汽車的電火花
Outer space. Or inner space.
外太空,或是地下
What if these people have an area of bilocation in their own living room?
但是如果有塊區域可以讓人同時在兩地出現?
What do you mean?
你什麼意思?
If that is the way out...
如果那就是出來的路...
then maybe somewhere in this house there's a way in.
那就是說這房子有進去的路
No, please. Leave it on.
別,開著吧
Thanks.
謝謝
You know, when it's quiet like now...
你知道,當這麼安靜時...
I can imagine how all of this must look from your side.
我就知道從你們的角度該如何審視這些事情了
I'm really embarrassed.
我真的很困惑
Nonsense.
廢話
I'm the one who should be embarrassed being here with you nice people.
我應該是那個跟你們來這受到困惑的人
Parapsychology isn't something you master in.
超心理學不是你該學習的東西
There are no certificates of graduation...
已經有兩個畢業證書...
no licenses to practice.
但卻沒有工作執照
I am a professional psychologist.
我是個專業心理學家
I spend most of my time engaged in this ghostly hobby.
我畢生都獻給了這些鬼鬼祟祟的事情
Which makes me the most irresponsible woman of my age that I know.
這讓我成了這個年齡段最難讓人接受的女人
Would you like a glass for that?
你不用拿個杯子嗎?
No, thank you.
不,謝謝
You know, you were very funny.
你知道,你很搞笑
Your hands were shaking about a mile a minute.
你的手抖的很厲害
This isn't over.
還沒結束
I'm absolutely terrified.
我十分的恐懼
It's all the things that we don't understand.
儘是些我們無法理解的事情
I feel like the protohuman, coming out of the forest primeval...
我感覺,那些猿人從原始森林走出來...
and seeing the moon for the first time and throwing rocks at it.
第一會看見了月亮,向它仍石子
If I got killed, would I come back...
如果我被殺了,我能回來...
and get stuck in the house like my sister?
像我的女兒一樣被陷在房子裡嗎?
Your sister isn't dead, Robbie.
你妹妹沒死
If I got killed...
如果我被殺了...
could I visit her and show her how to get back here?
我能去看望她,告訴如何出來嗎?
You could tie a rope around me and hold it tight...
你可以系跟繩子在我身上,緊緊的拉住...
then somebody could come and get us, and we could live somewhere else.
那麼人們就可以拉住我們不讓我們陷進去
Some people believe...
有人相信...
that when you die, your soul goes to heaven.
人死後靈魂會升入天堂
When Grandpa was dead...
外公死時...
I looked at him in the hospital bed and I was watching...
我在醫院的病床上看著他...
but I didn't see anything go up out of him.
但是我沒有見到有東西從他身上升起來
His soul is invisible, Robbie. You couldn't see it.
羅比,他的靈魂是看不見的
But how come Grandpa isn't on television with Carol Anne?
但是外公為什麼不和卡羅爾一起出現在電視上呢?
Some people believe that when people die...
有人相信人死後...
there's a wonderful light...
有個非常棒的燈...
as bright as the sun...
和太陽一樣明亮...
but it doesn't hurt to look into it.
並且並不刺眼
All the answers to all the questions that you ever want to know...
你所想知道所有問題的所有答案...
are inside that light.
都在這燈裡面
And when you walk to it, you become a part of it forever.
而當你走向它，你就永遠成了它的一部分
And then, some people die...
然後，一些人死了...
but they don't know that they've gone.
但是他們自己並不知道
They think they're still alive?
他們以為他們自己還活著?
Maybe they didn't want to die.
是的，可能他們並不想死
Maybe they weren't ready.
可能他們還沒有準備好
Maybe they hadn't lived fully yet...
可能他們還沒活夠...
or they'd lived a long time, but they still wanted more life.
或者他們已經活了很長時間， 但是他們還想繼續活下去
They resist going into that light...
他們拒絕走向那個燈光...
however hard the light wants them.
無論那個燈多需要他們
They just hang around...
他們留在了附近...
watch TV, watch their friends grow up...
看電視，看著他們的朋友長大...
feeling unhappy and jealous.
感到不開心和嫉妒
Those feelings are bad.
那些感情很不好
They hurt.
他們感到受傷害了
And then...
然後...
some people...
那些人...
just get lost on the way to the light...
失去了前往燈光的道路...
and they need someone to guide them to it.
他們需要有人來引導他們
So some people get angry...
所以那些人生氣了...
and throw things around, like in my bedroom?
並亂扔東西，像我的臥室一樣?
Just like in school.
就像在學校
Like, some kids are nice to you...
一些小朋友對你很好...
some kids are mean.
另一些對你刻薄
I got beat up once by three kids.
我有一次被3個小孩打了
They took my lunch money.
他們拿走了我的午飯錢
Maybe they got hit by a truck, and they're upstairs right now.
可能他們被卡車撞了，現在正在樓上呢
Listen, partner, maybe we oughta get some shut-eye, okay?
聽著, 也許我們該睡覺了，好嗎?
You know what?
你知道嗎?
When we called Grandma tonight...
當我們告訴奶奶今晚...
she got really excited that you're comin' to stay with her...
她很興奮你打算去陪她...
and she's plannin' all these neat things for you guys to do.
她打算好好接待你們
Can I take E. Buzz with me when we go?
我可以帶E. Buzz和我一起去嗎?
Sure you can.
當然可以
- Good night, Mom. - Good night, sweetie.
- 晚安，媽媽 - 晚安，親愛的
Night, lady.
晚安，女士
Night, Dad.
晚安，爸爸
Night, Rob.
晚安, 羅比.
I love you.
我愛你
Good night, Carol Anne.
晚安, 卡羅爾.
I'm gonna go get something to eat.
我想去找點吃的
What is it?
那是什麼?
Roll it back.
回放一下
I think we got one. I think it recorded.
我想我們應該已經錄下來了
Yes. It recorded.
是的，錄下來了
Look at all of them.
看看他們所有人
Is that our house?
那是我們的房子嗎?
Who are all those people?
那些人是誰?
They're so alone. So alone.
他們是這樣孤獨，這樣孤獨
Where are they coming from?
他們從哪裡來?
I don't know.
我不知道
Call me, okay?
打電話給我，好嗎?
This cameo is over a hundred years old.
這塊寶石已經有一百多年的歷史了
Yeah, some haul, huh?
是的，挺長時間了?
And this watch is only a few years old, and it's not yours.
而這塊表只有幾年的歷史，而它不是你們的
Well, I'm off.
嗯，我先走了
I'm taking these back to the lab along with the tapes.
我要帶著這些東西和錄像帶去實驗室
I'm going to have to display these, you know.
你知道，我不得不展示它們
- Please, not on "60 Minutes." - Or "That's Incredible!"
- 請不要再「60分鐘」上面 - 或是「難以置信」
I'll get it. Excuse me.
對不起
I'm leaving Ryan here with you.
我會把賴安留在這裡陪你
Marty won't be coming back.
馬蒂不會回來了
I am coming back.
我會回來的
And I'll bring some help.
並且我會帶回來一些有幫助的東西
Try not to worry.
不要擔心
Thank you.
謝謝你
We've missed you down at the office.
我們在辦公室很想你
The boys have gotten worried, so I took it upon myself to--
小伙子們很擔心，所以我過來看看--
Jesus, Steve, you look like shit. Aren't you feeling any better?
天啊，史迪夫, 你看上去很糟糕 你現在感到好點了嗎?
I'm still weak, Mr. Teague. I've got the flu, I can't get up--
我還是感到很虛弱，逖格先生 我感冒了，我起不來--
Looks like you got some cable problems here.
你這裡看上去好像有線電視壞了
Yeah. The cable's been off for a couple of weeks.
是的，有線壞了幾個星期了
We'll have to look into that. The rest of the block dark too?
我們應該查一查。 這個街區的其他用戶也壞了嗎?
No, just us.
不，只是我們
You got some electrical problems as well here.
你這裡電路好像也有點問題
What have you got screwed in there, a 300-watt bulb?
你把什麼東西裝這裡了，300瓦的燈泡?
You afraid of burglars, or are you trying to attract...
你怕遭賊，或是打算吸引...
every insect in Cuesta Verde?
在佛得角山脈的所有昆蟲?
- Steve, are you happy here? - Yes, I am, sir.
- 史迪夫, 你在這裡開心嗎? - 是的，先生
Forgive me for asking all these questions...
恕我冒昧問這些問題...
but we don't want to lose the best rep we've ever had...
但我們不想失去我們最好的職員...
to the flu or other opportunities.
因為感冒或是其他問題
Seeing all that software in your living room...
看了你起居室裡的所有軟件...
makes me wonder, maybe you've got something going on the side.
使我懷疑，也許你已經 得出點什麼東西了
No, I just read "Popular Mechanics." I got hobbies.
不，我只是在看 「普通機械學」 我有這嗜好
Feel like going for a little ride?
想兜兜風嗎?
I'd like to show you something.
我有點東西想給你看
Oh, God! I'm sorry!
哦，天啊! 對不起!
One of your children was born in your house, huh?
你的一個孩子是在這屋子 裡生下來的，對嗎?
I understand that she's missed a lot of school.
我理解她錯過了很多學校
One of Trask's daughters is in the same nursery class.
崔斯克的一個女兒也是在同一個護士班
She got the flu as well, huh?
她也感冒了，是嗎?
Yeah, we've all got the same thing.
是的，我們都感冒了
I'm sorry.
對不起
- I didn't see her. - She's around.
- 我沒看到她 - 她就在附近
I wonder if you'd mind if I asked you a question.
我想，你不介意我問你個問題吧
Are you thinking about leaving Cuesta Verde?
你是不是打算離開佛得角山脈?
How could anyone in the world have a problem...
為什麼這世界上的所有人在這樣 的一天都會有個問題？
How's that spot for a bay window?
這個位置放個落地窗不錯吧?
It's pretty nice if you're living up here, but...
你住在這裡的話是不錯，但是...
not so great down in the valley...
對於山谷裡來說...
Looking at homes cutting into the hillside.
看到山上有人家，就不怎麼好看了
You don't have to live in the valley anymore.
你不需要繼續住在山谷裡了
What are you saying?
你說什麼?
We're starting phase five right here where we're standing.
我們將在我們現在站的地方開始5個階段
All of this can be your master bedroom suite.
這裡可以成為你的主臥室套間
That can be your view. Interested?
那裡可以成為你的觀景台， 有興趣嗎?
Well, Mr. Teague, that's a generous offer.
嗯，逖格先生，你真大方阿
- I'm just not a developer. - You're responsible for 42o/o of sales.
- 我不是個開發商 - 你負責 42% 的銷售
That's almost half of everything down there.
那幾乎是下面所有的一半了
Almost $70 million worth of dwelling and properties.
幾乎是價值7千萬美元的房產
That's a whole generation of security...
那是一整套安全的發展計劃...
that nobody can put a price tag on.
沒人可以往上面貼價格標籤
I know we should have made you a full partner three years ago.
我認為我們應該3年前就使你 成為我們的完全合夥人
I don't want to lose you now.
我現在不想失去你
Not much room for a pool, is there?
這裡沒有空間造個游泳池吧?
We own all the land.
我們有整塊土地
We've already made arrangements for relocating the cemetery.
我們已經有了重新安排墓地的協議
You're kidding me.
你在開玩笑吧
- That's sacrilegious, isn't it? - Oh, don't worry about it.
- 這會遭天遣的，不是嗎? - 哦，不要擔心
After all, it's not ancient tribal burial ground.
畢竟，這不是古代部落的墓場
It's just... people.
這只是...人
Besides, we've done it before.
另外，我們以前也做過
When?
什麼時候?
In '76. Right down there.
76年，就在山谷裡
Cuesta Verde?
佛得角山脈?
All 300 acres. It was quite a deal.
總共300畝土地，挺大的生意
But I never heard anything about it.
我從沒聽說過
It's not something one advertises on a billboard...
這又不值得在廣告牌上登廣告...
or on the side of a bus.
或是登在汽車上
Don't worry. Friends and relatives can visit their loved ones...
不要擔心，朋友和親屬可以 在布朗斯頓公墓看望故去的人
It's only five minutes further.
只有5分鐘的路程
Oh, yeah. Five minutes. That's no great hardship.
哦，是的，5分鐘路程，不太遠
I suppose that would be okay.
我想應該沒問題
Okay with whom?
誰沒問題?
Whomever might complain.
可能會抱怨的人
Nobody's complained until now.
現在為止都沒人抱怨
We've had two experiences in the kitchen. This is the den.
我們在廚房有兩種經歷，這裡是房間
Y'all mind hangin' back?
你們不要跟過來好嗎?
You're jammin' my frequencies.
你們會干擾我的頻率
So... what side of the rainbow are we working tonight, Dr. Lesh?
那麼... 我們今晚研究彩虹的 哪一邊, 萊斯博士?
- This your Knott's Berry Farm solution? - I know what you're thinking.
- 這就是你的解決方案? - 我知道你在想什麼
But you must take my word for it. She's cleaned many houses.
但是你要記住我的話，她已經 驅清了很多屋子的鬼
Her gifts have been documented--
她的能力有所記載--
We haven't heard Carol Anne since last night.
那晚以後，我們沒再聽見過卡羅爾
Why is this door locked, Mr. Freeling?
這門為什麼鎖了，富勒裡先生?
- Answer her, Steven. - I am.
- 回答她, 史迪夫. - 我會的
I am addressing the living.
我是說那個起居室
I'm sorry.
對不起
That's the room my son and daughter used to occupy.
那個房間是我的兒子和女兒住的
We believe it's the heart of the house.
我們相信那是這個屋子的心臟
This house has many hearts.
這個屋子有很多心臟
- What is the matter? - What's the matter?
- 怎麼啦?
I was trying to answer her with my mind...
我試圖用我的意念來回答她...
and she couldn't hear me.
但她聽不見我
I thought you said this Tangina Barrons was an extraordinary clairvoyant.
我記得你說過坦基納 柏恩 具有透視能力
I am.
我是有
I just don't like trick answers.
我只是不喜歡欺騙性的答案
Come here, honey...
過來，親愛的...
and give me your hand.
把你的手給我
I'm not gonna bite you.
我不會傷到你的
Come on down here. You'll give me a whiplash lookin' up at you.
低下來點，讓我能夠俯視你
Your daughter is alive and in this house.
你女兒還活在這間屋子裡
Where was the last incident of bilocation?
最後一次事件發生在哪裡?
I get my strongest feelin'...
我強烈感覺到...
the point of origin is in the child's closet upstairs.
源頭起於孩子樓上的壁櫥
Yes. I believe that too.
是的，我也這樣相信
Honey, you're gonna be strong for me and for your daughter.
親愛的，你要為了我和為了你 的女兒而堅強點
I can do absolutely nothing without your faith in this world...
沒有了你的信心和對孩子的愛， 我什麼都做不了...
I will. Believe me, I will.
我會的，相信我，我會的
And will you do anything I ask, even if it comes contrary...
那你會照我說的做嗎？即使違背了 你作為一個人類和基督徒的信仰
Yes, I promise. Please!
是的，我會的
Would you all come on in?
你們都過來好嗎?
Gather 'round.
聚在一起
There is no death.
這裡沒有死亡
It is only a transition to a different sphere of consciousness.
只是另一種不同的意識的轉換
Carol Anne is not like those she's with.
卡羅爾和她身邊的東西不同
She is a living presence...
她是活生生地生存著的...
in their spiritual earthbound plane.
在他們的精神空間裡
They are attracted to the one thing about her...
他們被她的一樣東西所吸引...
that is different from themselves-- her life force.
對他們來說完全不同-- 她的生命力
It is very strong.
非常強大
It gives off its own illumination.
它散發出自己的光芒
It is a light that implies life...
它意味著生命的光輝...
and memory of love and home...
愛和家庭的回憶...
and earthly pleasures--
和現世的快樂--
something they desperately desire...
這是他們絕對渴望的...
but can't have anymore.
但卻再也沒有的
Right now, she's the closest thing to that...
現在，她最靠近...
and that is a terrible distraction...
那個可怕的娛樂物...
from the real light that has finally come for them.
有著來自他們的真實光線
Do you understand me?
你聽懂我說的嗎?
These souls, who for whatever reason are not at rest...
這些靈魂，不知什麼原因，沒有停息...
are also not aware that they have passed on.
也沒有意識到他們已經死了
They're not part of consciousness as we know it.
他們不是我們所知的意識
They linger in a perpetual dream state...
他們永遠徘徊於一種夢幻狀態...
a nightmare from which they cannot awake.
一個他們永遠醒不來的噩夢中
Inside the spectral light is salvation--
在七色光中是超度--
a window to the next plane.
隔著窗口看來世
They must pass through this membrane...
他們必須穿過這層隔膜...
where friends are waiting to guide them to new destinies.
那裡有朋友等著引導他們去新的目的地
Carol Anne must help them cross over...
卡羅爾必須幫助他們去穿越...
and she will only hear her mother's voice.
而她只能聽見她母親的聲音
Now...
現在...
hold on to yourselves.
要堅持住
There's one more thing.
還有件事
A terrible presence is in there with her.
一個可怕的東西在那裡和她在一起
So much rage. So much betrayal.
非常粗暴，非常狂野
I've never sensed anything like it.
我以前從沒感受過它這樣的
I don't know what hovers over this house...
我不知道什麼東西盤旋在這個屋子裡...
but it was strong enough to punch a hole into this world...
但是它有足夠的能力打個洞 來到這個世界...
and take your daughter away from you.
並帶走你們的女兒
It keeps Carol Anne very close to it...
它使卡羅爾非常靠近它...
and away from the spectral light.
遠離七色光
It lies to her.
它對她說謊
It says things only a child can understand.
它說些只有孩子聽得懂的話
It has been usin' her to restrain the others.
它利用她來控制其它幽靈
To her, it simply is another child.
對她來說，它只是另一個孩子
To us, it is the beast.
對我們來說，它是個野獸
Now let's go get your daughter.
現在，讓我們來找回你女兒
Red ribbons, handkerchiefs, tennis balls.
紅緞帶, 手帕, 網球
Okay, rope's ready.
好的，繩子準備好了
- Bathwater? - I shut it off. It's ready too.
- 浴缸裡的水呢? - 我關了，也已經準備好了
All right. Call to her.
好的，呼叫她吧
Carol Anne, it's Mommy. Can you hear me?
卡羅爾, 我是媽媽， 你聽得見我嗎？
Carol Anne, please tell Mommy hello.
卡羅爾, 請對媽媽說hello
Try again.
再試試
Can you say hello to Daddy?
你能對爸爸說聲Hello嗎?
Daddy and I miss you so much.
我和你爸爸都很想你
So much. We love you so much.
我們都非常想你，
Please, just say hello.
只要說聲Hello
- She's under restraint. - What?
- 她被壓抑住了 - 什麼?
- Who's restraining her? - There are many arms about her.
- 誰在壓抑她? - 她被許多手臂圍住了
She thinks it's safe. Who is she more threatened by, you or your husband?
她認為很安全。你們誰更能威嚇到她？ 你還是你丈夫？
Neither. Steve decides the punishment the children--
都不行。史迪夫判定對孩子們的懲罰--
That's not fair. I've never laid a hand--
不公平，我從沒打過他們--
Fight about it later. Steven, make Carol Anne answer you.
以後再吵，史迪夫, 讓卡羅爾回答你們
Be cross with her.
對她生氣
It's Daddy.
我是爸爸
Be angry with her, or you'll never see her again.
對她發怒,否則你將再也見不到她
Carol Anne, I want you to answer me.
卡羅爾, 我要你回答我
Tell her if she doesn't answer you, she'll get a spankin'.
告訴她，如果她不回答你， 你會打她屁股
- I've never spanked the children. - Honey, please. Just tell her.
- 我從不打孩子們 - 親愛的，不要這樣，告訴她
Carol Anne, you answer your parents...
卡羅爾,你快回答你的父母...
or you're gonna get a real spanking from the both of us!
否則我們都會狠狠地打你屁股
Mommy! Help me!
媽媽! 救我!
- She's away from him. - From whom? Is she all right?
- 她離開了他 - 離開了誰? 她還好嗎?
Diane, ask about the light.
達尼, 問問燈的事
Mommy, help me, please!
媽媽，請救我!
- Honey, do you see a light? - Help me, please!
- 親愛的，你看見一盞燈了嗎? - 請救救我!
Mommy! Help me!
媽媽，請救我!
Tell her to go to the light.
告訴她，去燈那裡
They'll follow her. They've been followin' her for weeks.
他們會跟著她， 他們已經跟著她幾個星期了
- You must do what I say! - Tell her, Diane.
- 你必須照我說的做! - 告訴她, 達尼.
Mommy, I can't find you!
媽媽，我找不到你!
Run to the light! Run as fast as you can!
跑向燈光那裡! 用你最快的速度!
- I am in the light! - No, honey.
- 我就在燈光裡! - 不，親愛的
- Tell her you are. - No, it's a lie!
- 告訴她，你在燈光裡 - 不，這是謊言!
You can't choose between life and death when dealin' with what is in between.
當你的孩子處於困境中， 你可以幫助她選擇生或死
Tell her before it's too late.
告訴她，否則會太晚了
Run to the light, baby.
孩子，跑向燈光那裡
- Mommy is in the light. - Tell her you're waiting for her.
- 媽媽就在燈光裡 - 告訴她，你在等她
Mommy is waiting for you in the light. I hate you for this.
媽媽正在燈光裡等你。 我討厭這樣做
Now clear your minds. It knows what scares you.
現在什麼都別想，它知道什麼能使你害怕
It has from the very beginning.
它從一開始就知道
Don't give it any help. It knows too much already.
不要給它任何幫助。 它已經知道的夠多了
Now, open the door.
現在，打開門
Ryan, get downstairs and wait by the target!
賴安, 下樓去等待目標!
Give me the tennis ball marked number 1 !
給我標記1的網球!
Dr. Lesh! It's my handwriting! It came right out of thin air!
萊斯博士! 是我的筆跡! 它憑空出現了!
The ball came back. It's his handwriting!
球回來了，是他的筆跡!
Kiss my ass!
他媽的!
Number 2!
2號球!
Give me your hand!
把你的手遞過來!
She's at the mouth of the corridor!
她就在走廊口!
Tell her to stop! Tell her not to go into the light!
告訴她停下! 叫她不要走到燈裡去!
Listen to me. Do not go into the light.
聽我說，不要走進燈裡去
Stop where you are. Turn away from it.
不管你在哪裡，停下來。 轉過身去
Don't even look at it.
甚至不要再看燈了
Hurry with the rope!
繩子快點!
Throw it into the light!
扔到燈光裡去!
Fantastic.
太棒了
I got it!
我拿到了!
Tell him to take up the slack gently.
告訴他慢慢拉繩子
Take up the slack!
拉繩子!
Help me tie this around my waist!
幫我把這圍在我腰上!
What are you doing?
你要幹什麼?
I'm goin' in after her!
我去把她帶回來!
She won't come to you! Let me go!
她不會跟你走的! 我去吧!
You've never done this before!
你以前從沒做過!
Neither have you!
你也沒有!
You're right. You go.
你是對的，你去
No! Let me!
不，讓我去!
You can't! Who's strong enough to stay here and hold the rope?
你不行！這裡只有你足夠 強壯能拉住繩子
I love you!
我愛你!
No! Go downstairs and wait by Ryan...
不! 到樓下去和賴安一起等...
and pull only when I say so!
聽到我命令的時候，用力拉!
Only when I say.
聽我的命令
Don't let go!
不要走開!
Never!
不會的!
It's coming.
來吧
How will we know she's got her?
我們怎麼知道她找到了她?
When will we know?
我們什麼時候能知道?
Cross over, children.
橫渡，孩子們
All are welcome.
歡迎你們所有人
All welcome.
歡迎
Go into the light.
走進燈裡吧
You said, "No" !
你說過，「不要」!
There is peace and serenity in the light.
燈裡有和平和寧靜
You said don't go into the light!
你說過不要走進燈裡!
Steven, not yet!
史迪夫, 還沒到時間!
- They're here! - They're back!
- 她們在這裡! - 她們回來了!
Diane! No, please, no!
達尼! 不要這樣，不要!
Get 'em into the water!
把她們放進水裡!
- Oh, God! - No, I'm helping you!
- 哦，天啊! - 不，我要幫你!
Don't worry.
不要擔心
Get 'em in the water. She's gonna be all right.
把她們放進水裡，她會好的
Come on. Breathe now.
來呀，快呼吸
Just take a breath. Breathe.
就吸一口氣，呼吸
Breathe. Damn it, breathe!
呼吸，他媽的，呼吸!
Breathe!
呼吸!
That's it. Come on.
快呀
Come on. Breathe. Yeah. That's it. Breathe.
快呀，呼吸，就是這樣，呼吸
Baby.
親愛的
Sweetheart.
甜心
Sweet pea, it's Daddy. Come on, honey.
寶貝, 我是爸爸
Come on, pumpkin.
快醒醒，小南瓜
Hi, Daddy.
你好，爸爸
This house is clean.
這房子乾淨了
Be careful.
當心
Mom, I'm going to dinner with Janice and Brian.
媽，我要去和賈尼斯和布賴恩一起吃飯
- Is your room packed up? - Everything but the bed.
- 你房間都收拾好了嗎? - 所有的東西，除了床
- Are we gonna sleep here tonight? - I guess not.
- 我們今晚睡在這裡嗎? - 我想不是
So you better get Brian to bring you home right after dinner.
所以吃完飯，最好馬上要布賴恩送你回來
Dad wants us to stay at the Holiday Inn on I-74.
爸爸要我們待在假日旅館 1-74.
Oh, yeah. I remember that place.
好的，我記住地方裡
You what?
你怎麼啦?
Are you gonna do anything about this?
你打算怎麼處理這個?
- About what? - Your new gray?
- 什麼? - 你的新灰髮?
Oh. You don't like it?
哦，你不喜歡?
You don't think it's kind of punk?
你不認為這有點龐克的味道?
Bye, Mom.
再見，媽媽
Honey, I don't know.
親愛的，我不知道
Okay, Rob. That thing almost killed me.
好的, 羅比.那東西差點殺了我
You okay? Don't hurt your back.
你還好嗎? 別傷了你的背
How you feelin'?
你感覺怎麼樣?
Oh, I'm good.
哦，我很好
I feel a little hung over, like I've been asleep for a few days...
我有點宿醉的感覺, 感覺好像睡了好幾天...
but... I feel good, Steven, I really do.
但... 我覺得很好, 史迪夫, 我真的感覺很好
She doesn't seem to remember any of it.
她好像什麼都不記得了
Oh, what a day.
哦，真棒的一天
Smell that mimosa.
聞上去像含羞草
You better cut a bouquet and take it with you. We're not stayin'.
你最好割束花帶著，我們不再住這裡了
I know.
我知道
We worked so hard for this.
我們為此而辛苦工作
A thousand beautiful memories.
1000個美妙的回憶
I gotta go to the office, pick up some stuff, clean up a few things.
我要回辦公室，整理點東西
I'll be back early.
我會早點回來
We're leaving tonight for sure?
我們今晚就離開嗎?
Yeah, we are.
是的
If the kids get sleepy, let 'em sleep 'til I get home.
如果孩子們睡著了，就讓他們睡到我回來
How's Teague taking it?
逖格怎麼想?
You know Teague. He won't take "Go to hell" for an answer.
你知道逖格. 他不會把「去死吧」 當作一種答案
- What will you tell him? - I'll give him directions.
- 你會告訴他什麼? - 我會給他方向
"...colored mixture generously directly from applicator to hair.
「...顏色混合後，慢慢從容器中塗到頭髮上」
- Gently work it through--" - Let me have that.
讓我來玩
I want my truck back. Stop!
我想要回我的卡車!
That's my truck!
那是我的卡車!
Gimme it.
給我
"Gently work it through with fingers to saturate every strand.
「慢慢用手指使頭髮吸滿
Then comb through with a brush and a comb...
然後用梳子梳理...
to be sure entire width of every hair is wet.
保證每根頭髮都濕
Do not lather."
不要太快」
- Get out of the solar system. - Gimme it.
- 滾出太陽系 - 給我
- It's getting late, guys.
- 很晚了，孩子們
- Give it back to me. - Give it.
- 把它給我 - 給我
- Stop it. - I'm gonna be in the bathtub.
- 停下 - 我要洗個盆浴
Could you answer the phone--
你能接電話嗎--
Could you answer the phone for me, please?
你能為我接電話嗎?
And can you tuck yourselves in, please?
你能自己睡覺嗎?
Yes, we will.
是的，我們能
Thank you. Good night, sweetheart.
謝謝你，晚安，甜心
- See what you get? - Good night.
- 看看你得到了什麼? - 晚安
- Good night, Robbie. - Good night, Carol Anne.
- 晚安, 羅比. - 晚安, 卡羅爾.
You're not real!
你不是真的!
Oh! Help!
哦，救命!
Help me!
救命!
You're not real!
你不是真的!
Let me go!
讓我走!
I hate you!
我討厭你!
You're done! I hate you!
你完了! 我討厭你!
Carol Anne, Robbie, run!
卡羅爾, 羅比, 快跑!
Open the door!
打開門!
Don't touch my babies!
不要碰我的孩子!
You-- Help me, somebody!
來人啊，救命!
No more.
不要
Mr. Tuthill!
杜希爾先生!
Ben! Help! Please help me!
本! 救命! 請救救我!
Somebody help me! Please!
來人救命啊!
Listen! What sort of sound is that?
聽著! 那是什麼聲音?
I've got to get them! Come on!
我要去救他們! 快來!
- What's going on? - Don't go!
- 怎麼啦? - 不要走!
- Please, Ben! Help me! - No, don't go!
- 本幫幫我! - 不，不要去!
Help me!
幫我!
Get away from my babies! Get away!
不要碰我的孩子! 滾開!
Help!
救命!
Give me your hand!
把你的手給我!
I can't reach you!
我夠不到你!
- Now grab your sister! - Take my hand!
- 現在抓住你的妹妹! - 抓住我的手!
Come on!
快!
Hold on!
抓住!
God, help me!
主啊，救救我!
Help us!
救救我們!
You moved the cemetery, but you left the bodies, didn't you?
你們搬走了公墓，但卻留下了屍體，是嗎?
You son of a bitch! You left the bodies and you only moved the headstones!
你們他媽的混蛋! 搬走了墓石 卻留下了屍體
You only moved the headstones!
你們只搬走了墓石!
Why?
為什麼?
Hurry, Dad, hurry!
快點，爸爸，快點!
- Dad, hurry! - Come on.
- 爸爸，快點! - 快來
Hurry.
快點
- Hurry, Dad! - Come on. Damn it, Steven, hurry!
- 爸爸，快點! - 史迪夫, 快點!
What's happening?
發生了什麼?
- Get in the car! - What is it?
- 進車裡! - 那是什麼?
Drive away! Daddy, drive away!
快開! 爸爸，快開!
Steven, hurry!
史迪夫, 快點!